<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Message Scheduler</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <!--    <string name="title_home">Home</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>-->
    <!--    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>-->

    <string name="status_upcoming">Upcoming</string>
    <string name="status_sent">Sent</string>
    <string name="status_delivered">Delivered</string>
    <string name="status_history">History</string>

    <string name="type_sms">SMS</string>
    <string name="type_whats_app">WhatsApp</string>

    <string name="msg_sent">Message sent successfully!</string>
    <string name="msg_delivered">Message delivered successfully!</string>
    <string name="msg_generic_failure">Generic failure!</string>
    <string name="msg_no_service">No Service!</string>
    <string name="msg_null_pdu">Null PDU!</string>
    <string name="msg_radio_off">Radio off!</string>
    <string name="msg_not_delivered">Message not delivered!</string>
    <string name="msg_no_whats_app_installed">WhatsApp is not installed on your device!</string>

    <!-- activity contacts -->
    <string name="selectReceiver">Select Receiver</string>
    <string name="searchName">Search by name…</string>
    <string name="searchGroup">Group name…</string>

    <!-- activity contacts dialogue -->
    <string name="txtViewGroupName">Group Name</string>
    <string name="txtViewNoItem">No Item Here!</string>
    <string name="deletePerson">R U Sure To Delete This Person?</string>
    <string name="personDeleted">Person Deleted Successfully</string>

    <!-- activity contacts group -->
    <string name="btnDone">Done</string>
    <string name="emptyGroup">Can\'t create Empty group!</string>
    <string name="groupCreated">Group contacts created successfully!</string>

    <!-- activity create group -->
    <string name="btnCreate">Create</string>
    <string name="createGroup">Create Group</string>
    <string name="groupName">Group Name Required!</string>
    <string name="readContactsPermission">Give us the permission to read your contacts!</string>

    <!-- activity edit schedule message -->
    <string name="txtViewName">Name</string>
    <string name="editTxtReceiverNumber">Receiver Number</string>
    <string name="editTxtMessage">Message</string>
    <string name="editTxtDate">Date</string>
    <string name="editTxtTime">Time</string>
    <string name="btnSMS">SMS</string>
    <string name="btnWhatsApp">WhatsApp</string>
    <string name="editScheduledMessages">Edit Scheduled Messages</string>
    <string name="enterValidDate">Please, Enter a valid Date!</string>
    <string name="enterValidTime">Please, Enter a valid Time!</string>
    <string name="enableAccessibility">Enable Accessibility</string>
    <string name="accessibilitySteps">When clicking on WhatsApp Button …\n○ More downloaded services\n○ WhatsappAccessibilityService\n○ enable Accessibility</string>
    <string name="receiverNumber">Receiver Phone Number Required!</string>
    <string name="validPhone">Enter a valid phone number!\nDigits only or choose from your contacts!</string>
    <string name="messageRequired">Message mustn\'t be empty!</string>
    <string name="messageSchedule">Message scheduled successfully!</string>
    <string name="sendMessagePermission">Give us the permission to send your messages!</string>

    <!-- activity forget password -->
    <string name="editTxtEmail">Email</string>
    <string name="btnSend">Send</string>
    <string name="emailSentSuccessfully">Email sent to you Successfully!\nPlease, check your email inbox.</string>
    <string name="emailSent">Email sent</string>
    <string name="passwordReset">Password Reset</string>

    <!-- activity schedule message -->
    <array name="messageType">
        <item>SMS</item>
        <item>WhatsApp</item>
    </array>
    <string name="txtViewAdvancedOption">Advanced Options</string>
    <string name="selectContact">You must select contact from the image on top of this screen not typing his info!</string>
    <string name="allContacts">You will see all contacts now if you press on the image above</string>
    <string name="whatsAppContacts">You will see only contacts that have WhatsApp now if you press on the image above!</string>
    <string name="validPhoneNumber">Enter a valid phone number!\nLIKE: 0106 320 8399\nLIKE: +201063208399\nor choose from your contacts by pressing on image on top of this screen!</string>
    <string name="permissionRequired">Your permission is required!</string>
    <string name="readContactsExplanation"><b>Read contacts</b>\nTo select recipients from your contact list</string>
    <string name="sendSMSExplanation"><b>Send SMS</b>\nIn order to send your scheduled messages</string>

    <!-- activity schedule network messages -->
    <string name="scheduleNetworkMessages">Schedule Network Messages</string>

    <!-- activity sign in -->
    <string name="editTxtPassword">Password</string>
    <string name="txtViewForgetPassword">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="btnSignIn">Sign In</string>
    <string name="txtViewSignInWith">Sign In With</string>
    <string name="txtViewDoNotHaveAccount">Do Not Have Account?</string>
    <string name="verifyEmail">Please, verify your email address to login.</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="emailRequired">Email Required!\nPlease, Type your Email!</string>
    <string name="passwordRequired">Password Required!\nPlease, Type your Password!</string>
    <string name="internetConnection">Your Data transfer and Wifi connection closed!\nOpen Internet Connection and try again!</string>

    <!-- activity sign up -->
    <string name="editTxtRePassword">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="btnSignUp">Register</string>
    <string name="txtViewAlreadyRegistered">Already Registered?</string>
    <string name="registerSuccessfully">Registered Successfully\nPlease, check your email for verification.</string>
    <string name="verifyAccount">Verify Account</string>
    <string name="authenticationFailed">Authentication Failed!\nThis Email already registered before!</string>
    <string name="commentError">Please, comment with error on play store to fix this error!</string>
    <string name="register">Create new account</string>
    <string name="validEmail">Valid Email Required!\nlike: example@example.com</string>
    <string name="passwordLength">Password should be at least 6 characters long!</string>
    <string name="confirmPassword">Confirm Password Required!\nPlease, Confirm your Password!</string>
    <string name="passwordIncompatible">Two passwords incompatible!</string>
    <string name="checkBoxRegisterPolicy">By registering, you agree to the</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="and">and</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditions">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>
    <string name="ofMessageScheduler">of Message Scheduler</string>
    <string name="warning">Warning</string>
    <string name="warningMsg">You must agree to the Privacy Policy and Terms &amp; Conditions of Use of Message Scheduler before proceeding</string>

    <!-- activity splash -->
    <string name="txtViewSplashActivity">Message Scheduler</string>

    <!-- row contact dialogue -->
    <string name="developerName">Ahmed Ali</string>
    <string name="developerNumber">+20 106 320 8399</string>

    <!-- row history person -->
    <string name="txtViewDateFormat">12/11/2019</string>
    <string name="txtViewDash">-</string>
    <string name="txtViewTimeFormat">02:36</string>
    <string name="txtViewMessage">any message could be here</string>

    <!-- bottom nav menu -->
    <string name="itemGroups">Groups</string>

    <!-- menu home -->
    <string name="itemMenuHome">Menu Home</string>
    <string name="itemTips">Tips</string>
    <string name="itemHelp">Help</string>
    <string name="itemEmailUs">Email Us</string>
    <string name="itemCallUs">Call Us</string>
    <string name="itemRateUs">Rate Us</string>
    <string name="itemProfile">Profile</string>
    <string name="itemSIM">Configure Networks</string>
    <string name="itemSettings">Settings</string>
    <string name="itemPrivacyPolicy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="itemTermsAndConditions">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>
    <string name="itemLogout">Logout</string>

    <!-- menu upcoming msg person -->
    <string name="itemEdit">Edit</string>
    <string name="itemDelete">Delete</string>

    <!-- menu search -->
    <string name="itemSearch">Search</string>

    <!-- activity networks -->
    <string name="SIMName">Network(SIM) Name</string>
    <string name="ExampleNetwork">LIKE: Vodafone</string>
    <string name="Prefix">Prefix</string>
    <string name="ExamplePrefix">Ex: +2010</string>
    <string name="simAdded">SIM Added Successfully!</string>
    <string name="configureNetworks">Configure Networks</string>
    <string name="simName">Network(SIM) Name required!</string>
    <string name="prefixRequired">Prefix of Network(SIM) required!</string>
    <string name="prefixRestriction">Prefix of Network(SIM) should starts with sign (+)!</string>
    <string name="prefixError">Prefix of Network(SIM) should be at least 2 digits!\nbased on your country, type the prefix of the network!</string>

    <!-- activity schedule group message -->
    <string name="scheduleMessages">Schedule Messages</string>

    <!-- activity select sim -->
    <string name="txtViewNoItemText">No Item Here!\nPress here to add Networks</string>
    <string name="selectSIM">Select Network(SIM)</string>
    <string name="deleteSIM">R U sure to delete this SIM?</string>
    <string name="simDeleted">SIM deleted successfully!</string>

    <!-- activity tips -->
    <string name="txtViewWarning">Your device may prevent this program (Messaging Manager) from working properly at its scheduled times if it has battery application management features or background processes</string>
    <string name="txtViewXiaomi">XIAOMI\'S DEVICE SETTINGS</string>
    <string name="textViewAutoStart">Auto Start (Important)</string>
    <string name="textViewStepAutoStart">Open Phone Settings > Permissions > Auto-Start > turn on for Message Scheduler.</string>
    <string name="textViewBatterySaver">Battery Saver</string>
    <string name="textViewStepBatterySaver">Open Phone Settings > Battery &amp; Performance > Choose apps > choose Message Scheduler > Choose no restrictions.</string>
    <string name="textViewBatteryOptimization">Battery Optimization</string>
    <string name="textViewBatteryOptimizationText">Disable Battery Optimization for Message Scheduler can help the app to work more reliably on Android 6.0 and higher.\nPlease notice that Message Scheduler doesn\'t use much battery.</string>
    <string name="btnDoItNow">Do It Now</string>
    <string name="textViewRecommendations">Further recommendations</string>
    <string name="textViewRecommendationsOne">* Because the setting may be different on your devices, so we\'d recommend that you recheck again on Phone Settings > Apps > Message Scheduler > Battery > and make sure that Message Scheduler is allowed to run as background and isn\'t restricted by Battery Optimization.</string>
    <string name="textViewRecommendationsTwo">* If your device includes some Battery Saver or Cleanup apps(for example: Cleanmaster, CM Suite, CCleaner, Battery Doctor, Greenify, and Amplify) make sure that Message Scheduler is added to whitelist.</string>
    <string name="textViewRecommendationsThree">* Enable Alert mode on App Settings > Advanced is strongly recommended.</string>
    <string name="tips">Tips</string>

    <!-- activity groups -->
    <string name="txtViewNoItemAddGroup">No Groups!\nClick Here to add Group</string>
    <string name="deleteGroup">R U sure to delete this group?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="confirmGroupDeletion">Group Deleted Successfully!</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="deleteMsg">R U Sure to delete this message?</string>
    <string name="confirmMsgDeletion">Message Deleted Successfully!</string>
    <string name="sendMsgNow">Message scheduled Successfully to now!</string>
    <string name="selectGroup">Select Group</string>

    <!-- activity privacy policy -->
    <string name="ppTextView">1. GENERAL</string>
    <string name="ppTextView2">Ahmed Ali built the Message Scheduler app as a free app. This SERVICE is provided by Ahmed Ali at no cost and is intended for use as is.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView3">This activity is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView4">If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView5">The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at Message Scheduler unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView6">1.1 Message Scheduler we understands that your privacy is important to you and that you care about how your information is used and shared online. We respect and value the privacy of everyone who uses our App and will only collect and use information in ways that are useful to you and in a manner consistent with your rights and our obligations under the law.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView7">1.2 This Policy applies to our use of any and all data collected by us in relation to your use of Our App. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully and ensure that you understand it. Your acceptance of Our Privacy Policy is deemed to occur when you first visit Our App AND/OR You will be required to read and accept this Privacy Policy when signing up for an Account. If you do not accept and agree to this Privacy Policy, you must stop using Our App immediately.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView8">2. WAYS THAT WE COLLECT INFORMATION AND USE OF THEM</string>
    <string name="ppTextView9">2.1 We have a legitimate basis for collecting, using and sharing information about you. If you are located within the European Economic Area (EEA), we collect and use your information in compliance with EU laws. The legal basis for collecting and using your data depends on how you use our Services. We only collect and use your information when one or more of the following situations apply:</string>
    <string name="ppTextView10">1. We need your information to fulfill our contract with you to provide and operate the Services you have requested as a Customer or Participant.\n2. There is a legitimate interest provided that such processing shall not outweigh your rights and freedoms. Examples include:</string>
    <string name="ppTextView11">1. Protect, monitor, prevent or investigate fraud or security threats\n2. Protect our legal rights and interests.\n3. For customer service.\n4. Manage corporate transactions, such as mergers or acquisitions.\n5. You give us consent to do so for a specific purpose\n6. The processing is necessary to comply with the law</string>
    <string name="ppTextView12">In situations where we rely on your consent to process personal data, you have the right to withdraw or decline consent at any time, however this will not impact any processing which has already occurred. Where we rely on legitimate interest, you have the right to object. However, this may mean you will be unable to continue using our Services. If you have questions about the lawful basis upon which we collect and use your personal information, please contact us at ahmdaliielsayed@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="ppTextView13">Types of Data Collected</string>
    <string name="ppTextView14">2.2 We may collect and securely process the following personal information or data about you, as they represent the minimum required for you to register with Our App and access/perform the services provided by it and While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (\"Personal Data\"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:</string>
    <string name="ppTextView15">1. Your full name\n2. Your email address\n3. Your profile picture\n4. Your scheduled content &amp; Recipients\n5. A record of any correspondence between you and us\n6. Your replies to any surveys or questionnaires that we may use for research purposes\n7. Details of your visits to the App and the resources that you access\n8. Information we may require from you when you report a problem with the App.\n9. Usage Data\n10. Data from Social Networks\n11. Third-party data\n12. Mobile device data</string>
    <string name="ppTextView16">2.3 We only collect such information when you choose to supply it to us, where it is securely stored and process according to best practices and laws &amp; regulations.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView17">2.4 Information is also gathered without you actively providing it, through the use of various technologies and methods such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. These methods do not collect or store personal information.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView18">2.5 An IP address is a number assigned to your mobile phone by your Internet Service Provider (ISP), so you can access the Internet. It is generally considered to be non-personally identifiable information, because in most cases an IP address can only be traced back to your ISP or the large company or organization that provides your internet access (such as your employer if you are at work).</string>
    <string name="ppTextView19">2.6 We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our server, report aggregate information, and determine the fastest route for your computer to use in connecting to our site, and to administer and improve the site.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView20">2.7 We may collect information from the use of Our App. When you use our mobile apps, we may collect certain information in addition to information described elsewhere in this Policy. For example, we may collect information about the type of device and operating system you use. We may ask you if you want to receive push notifications about activity in your account. If you have opted in to these notifications and no longer want to receive them, you may turn them off through your operating system. We do not ask for, access or track any location-based information from your mobile device at any time while downloading or using our Mobile Apps or Services. We may use mobile analytics software (such as Google Analytics) to better understand how people use our application. We may collect information about how often you use the application and other performance data.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView21">3. USE</string>
    <string name="ppTextView22">Usage Data</string>
    <string name="ppTextView23">When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, we may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data (\"Usage Data\").</string>
    <string name="ppTextView24">All personal data is stored securely.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView25">3.1 We uses the collected data for various purposes:</string>
    <string name="ppTextView26">1. Identify you when you login to your account\n2. Enable us to operate the Services and provide them to you\n3. Ensure that the content of the App is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your mobile phone.\n4. Assist in making general improvements to the App.\n5. Carry out and administer any obligations arising from any agreements entered into between you and us.\n6. Allow you to participate in features of the App and other services.\n7. Contact you and notify you about changes to the App or the services we offer (except where you have asked us not to do this).\n8. Analyze how users are making use of the App and for internal research purposes.\n9. To meet legal requirements, including complying with court orders, valid discovery requests, valid subpoenas, and other appropriate legal mechanisms\n10. To provide information to representatives and advisors, including attorneys and accountants, to help us comply with legal, accounting, or security requirements.\n11. To prosecute and defend a court, arbitration, or similar legal proceeding.\n12. To respond to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements\n13. To provide and maintain the Service\n14. To notify you about changes to our Service\n15. To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so\n16. To provide customer care and support\n17. To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service\n18. To monitor the usage of the Service\n19. To detect, prevent and address technical issues</string>
    <string name="ppTextView27">3.2 We will not resell your information to any third party nor use it for any third party marketing.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView28">3.3 Under GDPR we will ensure that your personal data is processed lawfully, fairly, and transparently, without adversely affecting your rights.  We will only process your personal data if at least one of the following basis applies:</string>
    <string name="ppTextView29">1. you have given consent to the processing of your personal data for one or more specific purposes;\n2. processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party or in order to take steps at the request of you prior to entering into a contract;\n3. processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation to which we are subject;\n4. processing is necessary to protect the vital interests of you or of another natural person;\n5. processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the controller; and/or\n6. Processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by us or by a third party, except where such interests are overridden by the fundamental rights and freedoms of the data subject which require protection of personal data, in particular where the data subject is a child.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView30">3.4 Some or all of your data may be stored or transferred outside of the European Economic Area (“the EEA”) (The EEA consists of all EU member states, plus Norway, Iceland and Liechtenstein). You are deemed to accept and agree to this by using Our Site and submitting information to us. If We do store or transfer data outside the EEA, We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated as safely and securely as it would be within the EEA and under the GDPR. Such steps may include, but not be limited to, the use of legally binding contractual terms between us and any third parties we engage and the use of the EU-approved Model Contractual Arrangements.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView31">✤ Transfer of Data</string>
    <string name="ppTextView32">Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView33">If you are located outside Egypt and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to Egypt and process it there.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView34">Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView35">Ahmed Ali will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView36">✤ Disclosure of Data</string>
    <string name="ppTextView37">Legal Requirements</string>
    <string name="ppTextView38">Ahmed Ali may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:</string>
    <string name="ppTextView39">✦ To comply with a legal obligation\n✦ To protect and defend the rights or property of Ahmed Ali\n✦ To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service\n✦ To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public\n✦ To protect against legal liability</string>
    <string name="ppTextView40">✤ Security of Data</string>
    <string name="ppTextView41">The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView42">4. SHARING YOUR INFORMATION</string>
    <string name="ppTextView43">4.1 We do not disclose any information you provide via the App any third parties except:</string>
    <string name="ppTextView44">1. If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation (for example, if required to do so by a court order or for the purposes of prevention of fraud or other crime).\n2. In order to enforce any terms of use that apply to any of the App, or to enforce any other terms and conditions or agreements for our Services that may apply.\n3. We may share information with our international partner websites where you have made a booking through the App with a user of our partner websites or where you have used the App to interact with a third party.\n4. We may, from time to time, expand or reduce our business and this may involve the sale and/or the transfer of control of all or part of our business. Data provided by users will, where it is relevant to any part of our business so transferred, be transferred along with that part and the new owner or newly controlling party will, under the terms of this Privacy Policy, be permitted to use the data for the purposes for which it was originally collected by Us. In the event that any of your data is to be transferred in such a manner, you will [not] be contacted in advance and informed of the changes.\n5. To protect the rights, property, or safety of Message Scheduler, the Apps users, or any other third parties. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.\n6. Service Providers: We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including, without limitation, hosting and maintenance, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services. Where any of your data is required for such a purpose, we will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data will be handled safely, securely, and in accordance with your rights, our obligations, and the obligations of the third party under the law. Service providers we are in contract with:</string>
    <string name="ppTextView45">1. Google Analytics\n2. Firebase\n3. Google Play Services</string>
    <string name="ppTextView46">4.2 Other than as set out above, we shall not disclose any of your personal information unless you give us permission to do so.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView47">5. ACCESS TO AND CORRECTION TO PERSONAL INFORMATION</string>
    <string name="ppTextView48">5.1 We will take all reasonable steps in accordance with our legal obligations to update or correct personally identifiable information in our possession that you submit via this App.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView49">5.2 We take all appropriate steps to protect your personally identifiable information as you transmit your information from your mobile phone to our App and to protect such information for loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. We use leading technologies and encryption software to safeguard your data, and operate strict security standards to prevent any unauthorized access to it.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView50">5.3 We do our best to keep your data accurate and up to date, to the extent that you provide us with the information we need to do so. If your data changes (for example, if you have a new email address), then you are responsible for notifying us of those changes. Upon request, we will provide you with information about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your Personal Information. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as long as needed to provide you with our Services. We may also retain and use your information in order to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, prevent abuse, and enforce our Agreements.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView51">5.4 You may withdraw your consent for us to use your personal data at any time by contacting us, and we will delete your data from our systems.  However, you acknowledge this may limit our ability to provide the best possible services to you.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView52">5.5 You have the legal right to ask for a copy of any of your personal data held by us (where such data is held). Please contact us for more details at ahmdaliielsayed@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="ppTextView53">5.6 Under the GDPR, you have:</string>
    <string name="ppTextView54">1. The right to request access to, deletion of or correction of, your personal data held by Us; The right to complain to a supervisory authority;\n2. Be informed of what data processing is taking place;\n3. The right to restrict processing;\n4. The right to data portability;\n5. Object to processing of your personal data;\n6. Rights with respect to automated decision-making and profiling.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView55">To enforce any of the foregoing rights or if you have any other questions about Our App or this Privacy Policy, please contact us using the details set out in section 9 below.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView56">6. OTHER WEBSITES</string>
    <string name="ppTextView57">6.1 This App contains links and references to other websites. Please be aware that this Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView58">6.2 We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of sites that are not operated by us, even if you access them via the App. We recommend that you check the policy of each site you visit and contact its owner or operator if you have any concerns or questions.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView59">6.3 In addition, if you came to the App via a third party site, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of the owners or operators of that third party site and recommend that you check the policy of that third party site and contact its owner or operator if you have any concerns or questions.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView60">7. YOUR VIEWS</string>
    <string name="ppTextView61">If you ever want to contact us to express your views on our privacy practices, or with any inquiries related to your personal information, or give your opinion or suggest an amendment to the application, you can do so via our contact page.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView62">If you have any questions about Our App or this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at ahmdaliielsayed@gmail.com. Please ensure that your query is clear, particularly if it is a request for information about the data we hold about you.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView63">✤ Children\'s Privacy</string>
    <string name="ppTextView64">Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (\"Children\").</string>
    <string name="ppTextView65">We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView66">8. UPDATES</string>
    <string name="ppTextView67">✤ Changes To This Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="ppTextView68">The App Policies and Terms &amp; Conditions may be changed or updated occasionally to meet the requirements and standards. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this activity.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView69">We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the \"effective date\" at the top of this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView70">You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.</string>
    <string name="ppTextView71">9. CONTACT US</string>
    <string name="ppTextView72">If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at ahmdaliielsayed@gmail.com</string>

    <!-- activity terms & conditions -->
    <string name="tcTextView">PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF USE AND CAREFULLY REVIEW THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS ON WHICH MESSAGE SCHEDULER OFFERS YOU ACCESS TO OUR SERVICES.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView2">1. DEFINITIONS</string>
    <string name="tcTextView3">Message Scheduler: Mean the people maintaining the scheduling app and any of its partners or group or associated companies.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView4">Conditions: Means these General Conditions of Use, including the Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView5">Services: Means any service that authorize the user to schedule a social media post, an email, a text message or a phone call</string>
    <string name="tcTextView6">Users/receivers: Means the person using the App to schedule Social Media Posts, Text Messages, Emails and Phone Calls</string>
    <string name="tcTextView7">Member: Refers any user of the App.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView8">Service: Refers to any service provided by the App to any Member.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView9">Receiver: Means any person receiving posts, messages, emails and phone call through Message Scheduler services.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView10">The App: Means Message Scheduler Mobile Application available on the Google Play store, operated and owned by Ahmed Ali.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView11">User Account: Means an account with the App opened by a Member and used in order to access the Service provided by the App.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView12">2. ABOUT USING THIS APP</string>
    <string name="tcTextView13">These terms apply to any use of the App whatsoever. By accessing the App, you are agreeing to be bound by Conditions in full. If you do not accept the Conditions stated herein, do not use the App.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView14">You agree to comply with the terms of the Good Conduct Charter and accept that your personal data may be processed in accordance with the Privacy Policy. In the event that you fail to comply with any of the Conditions Message Scheduler reserves the right to withdraw your Account in question and suspend or withdraw all Services without notice.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView15">3. VARIATION OF THE CONDITIONS, THE SITE AND SERVICES</string>
    <string name="tcTextView16">Message Scheduler reserves the right to modify the Conditions at any time by updating this posting. You should visit this page periodically to review the Conditions because they are binding on you. In addition, Message Scheduler may vary or amend the Services provided through the App, the app functionality and/ or the “look and feel” of the App at any time without notice and without liability.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView17">Any modification to the App, Services or Conditions will take effect as soon as such changes are published on the App.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView18">4. USER ACCOUNT AND ACCURACY OF INFORMATION</string>
    <string name="tcTextView19">User certifies to Message Scheduler that if User is an individual (i.e., not a corporation) User is at least 13.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView20">If you sign up for Message Scheduler on behalf of a company or other entity, you represent and warrant that you have the authority to accept these Terms on their behalf.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView21">In order to use the Services you must create a User Account and agree to provide any personal information requested by Message Scheduler. In particular, you will be required to provide your name, phone number, and email address.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView22">You agree and accept that all of the information you provide to Message Scheduler when setting up your User Account and at any other time will be true, complete and accurate in all respects.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView23">Message Scheduler will not be liable to any Member in the event that any information provided by a Member (including for the avoidance of doubt another Member), which is incomplete, inaccurate, misleading or fraudulent.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView24">5. LIABILITY</string>
    <string name="tcTextView25">Message Scheduler shall not be liable for any loss or damage arising as a result of:</string>
    <string name="tcTextView26">• Any inaccurate or incomplete information being provided by a User\n• Any fraud, fraudulent misrepresentation or breach of duty or breach of any of these Conditions by a User or Receiver.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView27">Message Scheduler will not be liable to any member for any business, financial or economic loss or for any consequential or indirect loss such as lost reputation, lost bargain, lost profit, loss of anticipated savings or lost opportunity arising as a result of the services provided by Message Scheduler (whether suffered or incurred as a result of the Message Scheduler’s negligence or otherwise).</string>
    <string name="tcTextView28">You agree to indemnify and hold us and our Team harmless from any losses, including attorney fees that result from any claims you make that are not allowed under these Terms due to a “Limitation of Liability” or other provision (Indemnity is an agreement to compensate someone for a loss). You also agree to indemnify and hold us harmless from any losses, including attorney fees that result from third-party claims that you or someone using your password did something that, if true, would violate any of these Terms.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView29">Attorney fees: If we file an action against you claiming you breached these Terms and we prevail, we’re entitled to recover reasonable attorney fees and any damages or other relief we may be awarded</string>
    <string name="tcTextView30">By displaying content on the App, you expressly grant a license to Message Scheduler to display the content and to use it for any of our other business purposes.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView31">Users of this App are expressly asked not to publish any defamatory, misleading or offensive content or any content which infringes any other persons intellectual property rights (e.g. copyright). Any such content is contrary to Message Scheduler’s policy and Message Scheduler does not accept liability in respect of such content, and the user responsible will be personally liable for any damages or other liability arising and agrees to indemnify Message Scheduler in relation to any liability it may suffer as a result of any such content. However as soon as Message Scheduler becomes aware of infringing content, Message Scheduler shall do everything it can to remove such content from the App as soon as possible.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView32">6. SUSPENSION OR WITHDRAWAL OF APP ACCESS</string>
    <string name="tcTextView33">Message Scheduler may terminate this Agreement at any time and for any reason by giving Notice to the other party. We may suspend our Service to you at any time, with or without cause. If we terminate your account without cause, we’ll refund a prorated portion of your monthly prepayment or reimburse you for unused credits. We won’t refund or reimburse you if there’s cause, like a violation of these Terms or our Acceptable Use Policy. Once terminated, we may permanently delete your account and all the data associated with it. If you don’t log in to your account for 12 or more months, we may treat your account as “inactive” and permanently delete the account and all the data associated with it.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView34">Message Scheduler does not allow accounts with the primary purpose of promoting or inciting harm towards others or the promotion of discriminatory, hateful, or harassing content. To this end, we may suspend or terminate your account if you send an email, SMS, WhatsApp, fb campaign, submit an advertisement or otherwise distribute any content that we determine, in our sole discretion, contains either of the following:</string>
    <string name="tcTextView35">1. A Threat of Physical Harm. This means any statement, photograph, advertisement, or other content that in our sole judgment could be reasonably perceived to threaten, advocate, or incite physical harm to or violence against others.\n2. Hateful Content. This means any statement, image, photograph, advertisement, or other content that in our sole judgment could be reasonably perceived to harm, threaten, promote the harassment of, promote the intimidation of, promote the abuse of, or promote discrimination against others based solely on race, ethnicity, national origin, sexual orientation, gender, gender identity, religious affiliation, age, disability, disease, or immigration status.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView36">We also may suspend or terminate your account if we determine, in our sole discretion, that you are either:</string>
    <string name="tcTextView37">1. An organization which has publicly stated or acknowledged that its goals, objectives, positions, or founding tenets include statements or principles that could be reasonably perceived to advocate, encourage, or sponsor Hateful Content or A Threat of Physical Harm.\n2. A person that has publicly made a comment or statement, or otherwise publicly made known a position, including by membership in an organization as discussed above, that could be reasonably perceived as Hateful Content or A Threat of Physical Harm.\n3. A person or organization that has acted in such a way as could be reasonably perceived to support, condone, encourage, or represent Hateful Content or A Threat of Physical Harm.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView38">In the event of non-compliance on your part with all or some of the Conditions, you acknowledge and accept that Message Scheduler can at any time, without prior notification, interrupt or suspend, temporarily or permanently, all or part of the services or your access to the App (including in particular your User Account).</string>
    <string name="tcTextView39">7. INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY</string>
    <string name="tcTextView40">All rights are reserved in relation to any registered and unregistered trademarks (whether owned or licensed to Message Scheduler), which appear on the Site and App. The contents of the App, such as text, publications, newsletters, articles, opinions, views, graphics, images, HTML code, multimedia clips, Java code and the selection and arrangement of information may not be reproduced, duplicated, copied, sold, resold, visited, or otherwise exploited for any commercial purpose.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView41">User shall not, nor permit anyone else to, directly or indirectly:\n(i) reverse engineer, disassemble, decompile or otherwise attempt to discover the source code or underlying algorithms of all or any part of the Service (except that this restriction shall not apply to the limited extent restrictions on reverse engineering are prohibited by applicable local law);\n(ii) modify or create derivatives of any part of the Service;\n(iii) rent, lease, or use the Service for timesharing or service bureau purposes; or\n(iv) remove or obscure any proprietary notices on the Service. As between the parties, Company shall own all title, ownership rights, and intellectual property rights in and to the Service, and any copies or portions thereof</string>
    <string name="tcTextView42">User shall not attempt to gain unauthorized access to any portion or feature of the Service, or any other systems or networks connected to the Service or to any Message Scheduler server, or to any of the services offered on or through the Service, by hacking, password “mining”, or any other illegitimate means.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView43">User shall not probe, scan or test the vulnerability of the Service or any network connected to the Service, nor breach the security or authentication measures on the Service or any network connected to the Service.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView44">User shall not take any action that imposes an unreasonable or disproportionately large load on the infrastructure of the Service or Message Scheduler’s systems or networks, or any systems or networks connected to the Service or to Message Scheduler.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView45">User shall not use any device, software or routine to interfere or attempt to interfere with the proper working of the Service or any transaction being conducted on the Service, or with any other person’s use of the Service.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView46">No party is entitled to systematically extract and/or re-utilize parts of the contents of the App without the prior written consent of Message Scheduler. In particular, the use of data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools to extract (whether once or many times) for re-utilization of any substantial parts of this App is strictly prohibited.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView47">8. LIMITATION OF WARRANTIES</string>
    <string name="tcTextView48">THE CONTENT MAY BE CHANGED WITHOUT NOTICE. THE CONTENT CONTAINED IN THE APP IS PROVIDED “AS IS” WITHOUT ANY REPRESENTATIONS, WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR USE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. FURTHER, NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES ARE MADE CONCERNING THE ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS, TIMELINESS OR RELIABILITY OF THE CONTENT, OR OF ANY INFORMATION CONTAINED IN ANY SITE LINKED TO THE APP. MESSAGE SCHEDULER DOES NOT WARRANT OR GUARANTEE UNINTERRUPTED ACCESS TO THE APP, ANY SITE LINKED TO THE APP OR TO THE AVAILABILITY OF INTERNET EMAIL LINKS PROVIDED ON THE APP. IN NO EVENT SHALL SKEDIT, ITS OFFICERS, AFFILIATES, AGENTS, LICENSORS, EMPLOYEES OR INTERNET SERVICE PROVIDER(S) BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO LOST REVENUE, LOST OR DAMAGED DATA OR OTHER COMMERCIAL OR ECONOMIC LOSS, WHETHER BASED IN CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE) OR ANY OTHER THEORY OF LIABILITY. THE FOREGOING LIMITATION SHALL APPLY EVEN IF MESSAGE SCHEDULER OR ITS OFFICERS, AFFILIATES, AGENTS, LICENSOR, EMPLOYEES OR INTERNET SERVICE PROVIDER(S) HAVE BEEN ADVISED OR SHOULD HAVE KNOWN OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView49">9. CONFIDENTIALITY</string>
    <string name="tcTextView50">Absent the use of encryption, the Internet is not a secured medium and privacy cannot be ensured. Internet email is vulnerable to interception and forging. Message Scheduler will not be responsible for any damages you or any third party may suffer as a result of the transmission of confidential information that you make to any third party through the Social Media Posts, Internet emails, Text Messages, Phone Calls links provided on the App. Message Scheduler is not responsible for any errors or any changes made to any transmitted information. Should you decide to transmit information using Message Scheduler Services, you do so at your own risk.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView51">10. PARTNER SITES</string>
    <string name="tcTextView52">Message Scheduler reserves the right to reproduce any information that appears on the App or on the partner sites.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView53">The site may contain links to other sites as well as email links. These links are provided solely as a convenience to you. These other sites were independently developed by parties other than Message Scheduler and Message Scheduler assumes no responsibility for the accuracy or appropriateness of the information contained in such sites. The inclusion of any link to another site does not imply endorsement by Message Scheduler. Any mention of another party or its product or service on the App should not be construed as an endorsement of that party or its product service. If you decide to access linked third party websites, you do so at your own risk.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView54">11. COMPUTER VIRUSES</string>
    <string name="tcTextView55">While Message Scheduler makes reasonable efforts to ensure that all Materials and Services provided on the App do not contain computer viruses, you are responsible to take the appropriate precautions to scan for Mobile App viruses and to ensure that you have a complete and current back up of the applicable items contained on your system.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView56">12. LAW AND JURISDICTION</string>
    <string name="tcTextView57">User also certifies that it is legally permitted to use the Service, and takes full responsibility for the selection and use of the Service. This Agreement is void where prohibited by law, and the right to access the Service is revoked in such jurisdictions.</string>
    <string name="tcTextView58">Even if this Agreement is terminated, this terms and conditions will continue to apply</string>
</resources>
